Guide to the Gerald Gunther Ppapers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2009-223
  - LH - Appelbaum, Alan, Esq. (Gerald Gunther), 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - C-LH - Ascoli, Max (name), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - C-LH - Auchincloss, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cromwell- LH - Austern, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Includes 1 audio cassette tape and transcript of GG and Austern interview, 1973.
  - C-LH - Bankruptcy Cases, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - GG-LH - Barbash, Joseph, Esq., 1970-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Includes transcript of GG and Barbash interview, 1970.
  - C-LH - Berenson, 1933-1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cromwell- Berenson, Bernard (1865-1959), 1949-1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Box 99 Materials. File 2 B. Berenson Notes and Bibliog., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Box 99 Materials. File 1 B. Berenson Notes and Bibliog., circa 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - C-LH Raoul Berger, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - C-LH Bibliography, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - GG-LH - Bliven, Bruce, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - GG-LH - Joseph Borkin, Esq., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Includes transcript of GG and Borkin interview, 1970.
  - LH- Boskey, Bennett (Gerald Gunther), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Includes transcript of GG and Boskey interview, 1970.
  - Braden, George D. (HLP) interview, 1970 May 13 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - LH-Brandeis, 1918-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Breuer, Ernest H., State Law Librarian, N.Y. State Library (GG), 1969 Nov 12 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - C-LH - Brown's Hotel, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Gerald Gunther - John Mason Brown Interview, 1968 Jun 12 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - C-LH - Bryn Mawr, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Burling, Edward B., 1967-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - LH- C.C. Burlingham, 1911-1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Includes transcript of GG interviews (2) with Burlingham, 1957.
  - LH-C.C. Burlingham - CCB-Cardozo Correspondence, 1921-1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - C-LH Burlingham - Letters to H. Croly from CCB Papers, 1918-1930 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - C-LH C.C. Burlingham Corres. With F.F. Notes - GG Notes (CCB Papers), 1936-1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Burlingham Cassettes, Transc. Master. - CCB Papers - GG Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - C-LH - Burlingham, 1957-1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - C-LH - James Byrne, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - C-LH - Cahn, 1952-1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - LH- Calkins, Hugh - Esq. (GG), 1969-1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Includes transcript of GG and Calkins interview, 1971.
  - C-LH - Cass Canfield, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - C-LH - Cardozo, Benjamin N., 1939-1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - LH - Cardozo Interview, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - C-LH Century Club, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cromwell-LH - Chafee, Zechariah (1 of 2), 1920-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cromwell-LH - Chafee, Zechariah (2 of 2), 1920-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - LH- Judge Harrie B. Chase, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Includes notes on GG interview with Chase, 1957.
  - LH- K.C. Clark, 1957-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - LH- W. Graham Claytor, Jr. (GG), 1962-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Includes transcript of GG and Claytor interview, 1970.
  - M.R. Cohen, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - LH-GG - Coleman, Mrs. Marjorie, 1943-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Includes transcript of Herbert Packer and Coleman interview, 1970.
  - LH- Cooper, James W. Esq. (GG), 1969-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - C-LH Copyrights, 1957-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - C-LH Cornish, N.H., 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - C- LH Cotton, Joseph, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - LH- Cox, Professor Archibald (GG), 1972-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Includes GG notes on conversation with Cox, 1973.
  - C-LH- Gardner Cox, 1978-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Includes transcript of Voss and Cox interview relating to Hand, 1987.
  - Croly, Herbert (LH), 1950-1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cromwell-LH - Mrs. Archie Cox, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Includes notes on GG interview with Cox, 1973.
  - HLP- Cutler, Lloyd, 1970 Oct 15 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Includes notes on interview with Cutler, 1970.
  - C-LH Danaher, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - C-LH Darrell, Norris, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - C-LH Davis, John W., 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - GG-Judge Edward J. Dimock Interview, 1968 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - GG-LH - Dorr, Goldthwaite H., Esq., 1913-1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Includes transcript of GG and Dorr interview, 1970.
  - C-LH W.O. Douglas, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - C-LH Louis Dow, 1944-1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - C-LH Ruth Draper, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - GG-LH - Dworkin, Ronald, M., 1969-1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - C-LH Eastman, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - HLP - Mr. and Mrs. Lawrence EBB Interview, 1970 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - C-LH - Thomas Ehrlich, 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - FAH - England, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - GG-LH - Ernest, Morris L. interview with GG and correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - C-LH Fabians, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - C-LH - FBI Report on LH, 1954-1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - LH- GG Filmscript, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - LH- Finkelstein, Herman, Esq. (GG), 1957-1990 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Includes transcript of GG and Finkelstein interview, 1970.
  - GG-LH Fisher, Benjamin C., Esq., 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - LH - Fitzwilliam, Robt. J. (J. Swan clerk 1946-47), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Includes transcript of Malloy and Fitzwilliam interview, 1970; 3 photographs of Hand.
  - C-LH Flexner, James Thomas and Forcey, Charles, 1956-1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - GG-LH - Forcey, Prof. Charles, 1956-1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Includes transcript of Hand interview, 1956.
  - Cromwell, LH- Frankfurter (1 of 2), 1919-1992 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Frankfurter, 1960.
  - Cromwell, LH- Frankfurter (2 of 2), 1919-1992 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - C-LH E.M. Forster, 1951-1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Frank, Judge and Mrs. Jerome (LH) (1 of 2), 1942-1987 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Frank, Judge and Mrs. Jerome (LH) (2 of 2), 1942-1987 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - C-LH Frankfurter (Parrish Biog.), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cromwell Project - Justice Felix Frankfurter, 1957-1987 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cromwell-LH - Frankfurter Papers, 1940-1987 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Frankfurter - Hand Supplemental Materials, 1913-1977 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - GG- Lawrence Z. Freedman Conversation, 1968 Aug 16 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - C-LH - GG - Hand Manuscripts (Personal + 1953-1954 Cases), circa 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - C-LH - Hand Research - Freedman, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - C-LH - Names - Paul Freund, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - C-LH - Freedom of Info. Act, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - LH - Friedman, Milton R., Esq. (GG), 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Friedman, 1970.
  - LH- Judge Henry J. Friendly, 1970-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Includes transcript of Packer interview with Friendly, 1970.
  - C-LH Lon L. Fuller, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cromwell- LH Goldman, Max, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Includes notes on GG interview with Goldman, 1973.
  - GG-LH- Goroski, Mitchell (Research Assistant), 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Includes Goroski notes on interview with Carmichael, 1971.
  - LH- Cromwell - George T. Gregory, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - GG-LH Daniel M. Gribbon, Esq., 1944-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Gribbon, 1970.
  - LH- Erwin N. Griswold, 1931-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cromwell LH-GG, 1955-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Includes transcript of GG and Packer interview, 1971.
  - GG-LH - Gurfein, Murray I., Esq., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Includes transcript of GG and Gurfein interview, 1970.
  - C-LH - Richard Hallet, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - C-LH - Philip Hamburger, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - C-LH - Hamilton, H., 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - C-LH A.N. Hand, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - C-LH Hand, Frances A., 1915-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - C-LH Hand Law Clerks, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Includes list of Hand law clerks.
  - C-LH Mary Hand, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - C-LH Hand Photos, 1956-1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Negatives included.
  - Harlan, Justice John M. LH Cromwell (HLP interview), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - LH - Harris, Prof. Robert (GG), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - C-LH Harvard, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - GG-LH - Hawes, Alexander Boyd, Esq., 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - C- LH - Names - Helmes, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - LH - Henkin, Professor Louis (HLP), 1970 May 14 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Includes transcript of Packer interview with Henkin, 1970.
  - GG - Ben Herzberg Interview, 1968 Oct 30 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - C-LH - Names - F. Shapiro Hochberg, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - GG-LH - Malcolm A. Hoffman, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - LH-GG Hollands, Prof John. H., 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - C-LH - Holmes (1 of 4), 1918-1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - C-LH - Holmes (2 of 4), 1918-1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - C-LH - Holmes (3 of 4), 1918-1992 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - C-LH - Holmes (4 of 4), 1918-1992 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - C-LH - Horsky, Charles A. (HLP interview), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - LH- Charles M. Hough, 1913-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Chapter IX: Hoover Years and Hand's Missed Chance, 1930-1956 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Newspaper Articles and Frankfurter on Hughes
  - C-LH Illustrations, 1959-1988 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Includes photos/negatives.
  - James, William, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - C-LH Wm. T. Jerome, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - C- LH Johnson, Alvin, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - LH- Johnson, Stuart H., Jr. -Esq. (GG), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - GG-LH - Judge Orrin G. Judd (Brooklyn NY), 1953-1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Judd, 1970.
  - C-LH - Judicial Salaries, Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - C-LH - Kaufman, I., 1983-1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - C-LH - J.B. Kennan, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - C-LH - Keynes, John Maynard, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - C-LH - Constance Kidde, 1957-1973 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - GG - Frederic R. King Interview, 1968 May 22 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - GG-LH - King, Rufus, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    Includes transcript of Packer interview with King, 1970.
  - C-LH - Laguardia, Fiorello, 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - C-LH - Harold Laski, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - C-LH - Law Clerks, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - C-LH - Learned Family, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - LH- Leiman, Leonard M. (GG), 1957-1979 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Leiman, 1970.
  - C-LH - Lemann, 1952-1980 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - C-LH - Edward Levi, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - GG- Wilmarth Sheldon Lewis Interview, Farmington, Conn., 1970 Mar 10 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - GG - Walter Lippmann Interview (1 of 3), 1969 Jan 22 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Includes notes on GG interview with Lippmann, 1969.
  - GG - Walter Lippmann Interview (2 of 3), 1969 Jan 22 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - GG - Walter Lippmann Interview (3 of 3), 1969 Jan 22 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - C-LH Llewellyn, K.N., 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - L. Hand - Archibald MacLeish, Esq., 1943-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Includes transcript of GG and MacLeish interview, 1970.
  - C-LH Magruder, Calvert, 1939-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - C-LH - Manton, (1920s refs. in Taft Papers), Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Mack, Judge Julian, 1922-1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - J. Maguire (Kirschenbaum Case), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - C-LH - Masses Case (1 of 2), 1981-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - C-LH - Masses Case (2 of 2), 1981-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - C-LH McCarthyism, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - GG-LH McKusick, Vincent L., Esq., 1970-1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - C-LH Medina, Judge Harold R., 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - GG - Judge Harold R. Medina - Interview, 1968 May 21 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Medina, 1968.
  - C-LH - Merz, Charles, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - C-LH - Mildred Minturn, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - GG-LH - John D. Molloy, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Includes transcript of tape recorded by Molloy on LH, 1971.
  - C-LH - Montaigne, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - National Archives - LH - Judicial Appointments, 1918-1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - C- LH - Neurasthenia, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Cromwell - Morris, (Mrs. Newbold) Constance Hand, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - C-LH - Morrow, Dwight, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Obituaries - CA2 Judges (NY Times, etc), 1925-1975 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - GG - John Lord O'Brian Interview, 1968 Oct 29 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Includes Transcript ofGG and O'Brian interview, 1970; notes on GG and O'Brian interview, 1968.
  - Obituaries, 1923-1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - C-LH Obituaries (LH, Hapgood, Rublee, etc.), 1906-1961 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Index to obituaries included.
  - C-LH - Olcott, 1913-1992 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Cromwell-LH - Packer- G.G. Interview, 1957-1971 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Packer, 1971.
  - C-LH - Obscenity, 1957-1988 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - C-LH - Patents, 1929-1983 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - LH- Pont, Manard E., 1951-1978 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - GG - Judge Edmund J. Palmieri - Correspondence and Interview, 1970 Mar 9 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Palmieri, 1970.
  - LH- Parker, John J. (Judge), 1930-1985 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - C-LH - Patterson, Robt., 1971-1988 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - C-LH-Platt, 1973-1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - HLP- Richard Paul-Jay Topkis Interview (transcript), 1970 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - C-LH - Posner File, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - C-LH - Roscoe Pound, 1916-1986 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Loose correspondence, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Cromwell-LH - T.R. Powell, 1932-1988 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - C-LH - Price Index, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - C-LH - Prohibition, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - C-LH - Rabban, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - C-LH - Reed, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - C-LH - Remington File, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - C-LH - Richardson, 1980-1991 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - C-LH - Rifkind, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - C-LH - Reese, Willis (Professor), (HLP Interview), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Includes transcript of Packer interview with Reese, 1970.
  - GG-LH - Richardson, Elliot L., 1951-1992 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Robinson, Dr. John L., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - C-LH - F.D. Roosevelt, 1942-198? (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - C-LH - T. Roosevelt, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - C-LH - Rublee, 1964-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - C-LH - Russell, Bertrand, 1952-1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - C-LH - Rutter, Irvin C., 1961-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - C-LH Sacco-Vanzetti, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - C-LH - J.D. Salinger, 1984-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - GG-LH - Sacks, Albert M., 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Includes transcript of Sacks interview with Jack Molloy on Hand, 1970.
  - Santayana, George, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - GG-LH - Schick, Marvin, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - C-LH - Scott, Austin W., 1929-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - C-LH - Samuel Seabury, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - C-LH - Seavey, 1941-1959 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Cromwell-LH - Michael E. Smith, 1973-1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - C-LH - Speciale, Michele, 1945-1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - C-LH - Steel, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - C-LH - Henry L. Stimson, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - C-LH - Stone, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - C-LH - Supreme Court Appointment, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cromwell- Judge Thos. W. Swan, 1958 Jul (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - C-LH Taft, 1924-1992 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cromwell- Thayer, Jas. Bradley, 1897-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - C-LH Thayer, 1897-1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cromwell-LH - Thayer, L. Harrison, Jr., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - C-LH Torts, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - LH - Von Mehren, Robert B., Esq. (GG), 1969-1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - C-LH - G. Wallas, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - LH - Wiener, Frederick Bemays (GG), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - C-LH Weinstein, circa 1987 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - C-LH West Point Scandal, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - GG-LH- Willner, Sidney H., Esq., 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Includes transcript of GG interview with Willner, 1970.
  - C-LH - Woodrow Wilson, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - LH - Richard F. Wolfson, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - LH - Wright, Charles Alan (Prof. U. Texas L.S.) (GG), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - GG-LH - Wyzanski, Chas. E., 1935-1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Yale Library, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - GG-LH - Prof. Adam Yarmolinsky (interview with J. Malloy), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - GG-LH - Y ounger, Irving, Hon., 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - LH - Youngman, William Sterling (GG), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - C-LH - Correspondence 1990 #23 (1 of 3), 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - C-LH - Correspondence 1990 #23 (2 of 3), 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - C-LH - Correspondence 1990 #23 (3 of 3), 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - C-LH - 1989 Correspondence #22 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - C-LH - General Correspondence #21, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - LH - Basic Overview Material, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - C-LH Publications (1), 1967-1989 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Includes correspondence related to publication of Hand biography.
  - C-LH Publications (2), 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - C-LH Flood Damage, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Cromwell Project - Lists - clerks, interviews, etc., 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Cromwell Proj ect Oral History, 1962-1968 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Cromwell-LH - Smith (Packer) History, 1973 Mar (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - LH Research Notes, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - C-LH Hand Research - Lexis, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - C-LH Hand Research - Library of Congress, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Research Memos and Outlines, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Cromwell Project Staff, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Cromwell- Second Circuit Judges biographical and bibliographical data, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cromwell Project- LH - Research, 1969-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - C-LH - Hand Papers Shipment List, 1972-1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hand and Sup. Ct. 1942, Library of Congress - FF Papers esp. w/CCB, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gerald Gunther - Norris and Mary Darrell Interview, 1968 Jun 11 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Includes notes on GG interview with the Darrells, 1968.
  - Gerald Gunther - Mary Hand Darrell Interview, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Includes transcript of July 24, 1970 GG interview with Mary Hand Darrell
  - Gerald Gunther - Constance Hand Morris Interview, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Includes 2 audio cassette tapes and transcript of August 3, 1973 GG interview with Constance Hand Morris
  - LH- GG - Ferguson, Mrs. Robert, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Includes transcript of interview with Ferguson, 1970.
  - Cromwell Project - Progressives, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - C-LH - Psychobiography, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - C-LH - Psycho History, 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - C-LH - Research - LH Congr. Committee Appearances, 1919-1955 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cromwell LH Research #9, 1977-1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Cromwell LH Research #8, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cromwell LH Research #7, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cromwell LH Research #6, 1960-1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cromwell LH Research #5, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Cromwell LH Research #4, 1957-1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cromwell LH Research #3, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Cromwell LH Research #2, 1958-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cromwell LH Research #1, 1963-1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - C-LH - Hand - Tax Cases, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - C-LH - Yale Mss. Holdings, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - C-LH - Research of Sources, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - C-LH - Return to Harvard, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Hand Student Research Needed, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 99, F. 7, Charles Lowell Barlow, 1908-1912 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 99, F. 8, Charles Lowell Barlow, 1929-1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 99, F. 10, Gordon Knox Bell, 1911-1921 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 99, F. 11, Gordon Knox Bell, 1932-1955 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 100, F. 1, Robert P. Bowler, 1897-1902 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 100, F. 2, Robert Pendelton Bowler, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 100, F. 3, Louis D. Brandeis, 1926-1937 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 100, F. 25, C.C. Burlingham, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 100, F. 26, C.C. Burlingham, 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 100, F. 27, C.C. Burlingham, 1919-1924 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 101, F. 7, Benjamin N. Cardozo, 1913-1926 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 101, F. 8, Benjamin N. Cardozo, 1926-1929 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 101, F. 9, Benjamin N. Cardozo, 1930-1933 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 101, F. 10, Benjamin N. Cardozo, 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 102, F. 17, Herbert Croly, 1909-1910 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 102, F. 18, Herbert Croly, 1910-1911 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 102, F. 19, Herbert Croly, 1911-1912 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 102, F. 20, Herbert Croly, 1912-1913 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 102, F. 21, Herbert Croly, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 102, F. 22, Herbert Croly, 1913-1914 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 102, F. 25, Herbert Croly, 1922-1924 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 102, F. 26, Herbert Croly, 1925-1930 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 1, Felix Frankfurter, 1910-1912 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 2, Felix Frankfurter, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 3, Felix Frankfurter, 1913-1914 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 4, Felix Frankfurter, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 5, Felix Frankfurter, 1915-1916 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 6, Felix Frankfurter, 1916-1917 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 7, Felix Frankfurter, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 8, Felix Frankfurter, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 9, Felix Frankfurter, 1920-1921 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 10, Felix Frankfurter, 1921-1923 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 11, Felix Frankfurter, 1923-1924 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 12, Felix Frankfurter, 1925-1926 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 13, Felix Frankfurter, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 14, Felix Frankfurter, 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 15, Felix Frankfurter, 1928-1929 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 16, Felix Frankfurter, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 17, Felix Frankfurter, 1929-1930 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 18, Felix Frankfurter, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 19, Felix Frankfurter, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 20, Felix Frankfurter, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Photocopies of Transcriptions, Box 104, F. 21, Felix Frankfurter, 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 50)